It's an eye.
Yeah, I finished it all.
I worked so hard so I could confess my feelings.
Ugh, I just want to roll over and die.
Mookie never showed up to meet me that night.
And after that, all I received was a lame message.
He didn't even bother telling me how it went for him.
Seriously? Is he trying to piss me off?
I can't believe it. Did things actually go well for him?
That's so stupid.
He's obviously being tricked by that hussy.
Are you stupid? All of them just want to be tricked.
Right. That's what all men want.
I do.
oh wow it feels really nice up here Karuizawa is this a heartbreak trip or a grieving trip
and for two suitors nonetheless that's not true nothing even started with one of them
aren't summer resorts just great the wind feels so refreshing I guess it's because of the fog and
terrain out here what's the harm in it look nobody is ever going to know us out here we're just here by
ourselves I should have known Sanai is pretty forward in situations like these don't look at
me like that that's so unfair to be honest it is better when I can keep my mind busy after all I did
just have my heart broken Hanabi thanks for coming with me I mean it so anyway that's a pretty amazing
having a vacation home oh yeah it's not really ours it's a relatives don't expect much it's pretty old
are you kidding this is great I'm glad then and there's nobody else here we get to be all alone
so please do come you're welcome to come in huh what
yikes this is a bit awkward are you enjoying the food yeah I am it tastes really great what about you
Sanai it's fine because you made it Atsuya he looks just like Sanai especially his profile
Hanabi why don't you take a bath first are you sure shouldn't I help we're good here aren't you tired
yeah okay then it feels so nice and warm soaking in here but I feel a little self-conscious
though the view is quite amazing
you're too close to me am I the kitchen is pretty small out here don't you think Sanai
are you mad of course I'm mad how mad just guess
you're still just as pretty when you're mad just shut up and wash
I didn't bring any clothes with me not my fault back up or get wet
things are heating up out there you're not forgiven and you never will be
how did you even know we were coming here I called your house we were going to get to be alone
it was my chance she got her heart broken and broke up her relationship
were you planning on making her yours on this trip that's right and you've ruined it all I didn't ruin
anything you have to realize by now that she'll never fall in love with you
you wanted one last time a memory to share
shut up
well you're the one being louder than me right now
do you really think it's that wrong to want things to end on a good note
I want you to end things cleanly I really do but I don't think you're strong enough for it
not with her
just shut up you better not try and come in our room tonight
then try and keep it down
why what's the problem
what do others know about me that I don't
your body is so hot because I just took a bath
you smell really nice too
I haven't shown anything of myself
I don't want anyone to get to know me
are we doing it tonight
yes of course
but we're not alone here
he's in the next room over
so keep your voice down
even after touching her
even after falling in love
I still choose to be alone in the end
and what's so wrong with that anyway
I choose my own ending
I can't go back to sleep
Hanabi
a notebook
is it so nice
it's a bullet train ticket
it says it's to Karuizawa
did she keep it?
you okay?
you're still shaking
please take this
I know it's not a lot but
how did I become so fragile
that a touch could break me
and yet
here I am
I keep on breathing
and my heart keeps on beating
oh
I see you're up early
you too
you want to take a walk?
I don't see lakes that often
it's beautiful
me either
hey Hanabi
who are you interested in?
uh
hey
where did that come from?
just answer me
well
I
I don't know
I'm still confused
maybe I should have worded it
a bit clearer for you
at least decide
how you feel about Sanai
I don't care about the rest
listen here
Sanai isn't just someone
you use as a replacement
you need to decide during this trip
I know
he's right about that
I should already know by now
oh my god
this place is so awesome
I know how you love buying clothes
wow
I bought so much
we got everything we wanted
I think I used up all the money
I earned over the summer
it's been a while since you looked this happy
that's good at least
the shade is nice over here
yeah it is
there
jeez
you need to watch where you throw this
I'm sorry about that
I know
listen here
Sanai isn't someone you use as a replacement
what is this?
I should know already
am I feeling possessive now?
this isn't love
the truth is
I guess
why you start
it's been a misunderstanding
since the beginning
together
it won't change anything
no
it can't
this feeling is
please
at least for now
nobody put a label on this feeling
I promise
this is the end
we're back
jeez
you just distracted me in my game
why are you playing something that's so old?
they only have retro games here to play
wait
are you sick?
welcome back
are you going to be alright?
I'm fine
I'm taking a nap
wouldn't want you sick
you need to decide during this trip
I can't believe I died again
how many was that?
you suck at this Sanai
you're actually good at this
I used to play a lot when I was hanging over at brother's house
no
I'm fine
I'm okay now
really
I guess Mr. Kanai was the person
the one you've been so in love with
although he completely rejected me
I actually feel refreshed about the entire thing
come to think
oh
damn it
not now
now's not the time to cry
I'm proud of what you did Hanabi
you really went for it
but it still didn't matter what I did
I never had a real chance with you
oh god
Sanai
I
there's something I really need to tell you now
Hanabi
this time it's me
I need to have an answer
sorry for making you spend time with me
thank you
you were always so nice to me
no
I'm sorry for having forced myself on you
I know I've been selfish with you
no
it was fun though
and I was happy
so from now on
no
you don't have to
stop it
I took advantage
I'm the selfish one here
it was all me
so I'm
it's fine Hanabi
it's time
I need to let you go
I already made my decision before the trip
that even after you got rejected
if you still didn't
look at me in the way that I long to look at you
then I decided
I would distance myself from you
why Sanai
it's too hard
I'll sleep in a different room
let's leave separately tomorrow
goodnight
Sanai
don't you understand
I'm not a nice person at all
Sanai
look at me
there's something that I really needed to say to you
Sanai
please continue staying friends with me
are you kidding me
just stop already
do you have any idea how cruel that is to do to me
how can I just go back to being friends
after everything
you don't even know
you don't even know how much I
really loved you
of course
it was raining
that day
I realized my weakness
my mistake
I'm ashamed I caused you this much pain
I won't give up this time
I'll fix it
I know Sanai
that you said you didn't need anyone
to know what's really inside your heart
but come on
that's no different than being alone
even if we continue things as they are
or even if we end them all together
the door to your heart still remains shut
listen
I'm fine being alone
so just leave me
stop trying to come inside
no don't
I'm going to
please Sanai
I want to know all of you
I want to know everything that I possibly can about you Sanai
just tell me all of it
I'll wait for you
please
you're all I have now
I know I'm nothing but worthless
deep down I'm a monster
I know you'll just come to hate me
how do you think I could ever get over that
I promise I'll wait
until you're ready
I'm scared
I'm so scared right now
why can't I
just be happy with being alone
oh no
I just realized
it's not just me
you also have the same frightened eyes that I have
okay
I don't know when I'll be ready though
I still love you way too much
but
I'll try
I'll do my best
to forget
I know I have to forget this
but I don't want to forget this taste
huh
hey did your friend leave already
yeah she did
she left early
that's a shame
well then
I didn't get to talk to her at all
that's enough talking
now just let me take care of you
Sanai
you did your best
shut up will ya
and hurry and get your fever down
so we can leave
you know you'll still always have me
hmm
I guess so
what
you know what it's like
maybe I'll try trusting you more
I don't know what's going to happen
now we're in the future
that's why I'll believe
I have to
I'll wear this feeling like a charm
something that feels warm inside your heart
it's been a while since I've been here
the school
the classroom
the reason for this uncomfortable feeling
all this loneliness
isn't because it's a new semester
I know that
it can't be helped
it still hurts
it still stings
what can you do
whoa
Noriko is wolfing down that bread
she looks insane
maybe she's just hungry is all
yes
that was awesome
what's with the gloomy face all of a sudden
oh
you going home alone
and your point
poor horrible thing
did you get rejected too
what do you mean rejected too
seems to me you've always been rejected this whole time
what
why do you have to be so annoying
you're the annoying one
what do you want
what do you have to say to me
that I've loved my precious Mookie much longer
and more honestly than you could ever dream of
I feel refreshed and alive now
it means the Danish you get at the school store yourself
can still taste as good
you'll understand once you bother doing something for your own well-being
isn't that interesting
I was just standing here in this world
feeling that I was all alone
I wonder why
it never even occurred to me till now
I can walk out on my own
it's strange
isn't it
I guess they call this a home visit
I've always admired them
getting to meet the parents
being served tea
just stop it
stop acting like a teacher
I don't think so
you know why
because I really am a school teacher
but I
I can't
why not
it's not a lie
come on
now say it
teacher
it's true
I honestly did come here for an official home visit
teacher
this isn't my fault
the parents weren't home
I found myself all alone
with just this boy
that's why
it couldn't be helped
how could it
it
You
you